<resources>
    <string name="app_name">"World's Best Places to Visit "</string>
    <string name="reef1">"As one of the Seven Natural Wonders of the World,
the Great Barrier Reef holds a spot on every traveler's bucket list.
 Hugging the east coast of Queensland, Australia, the Great Barrier Reef
 extends from Cape York in the north all the way to Bundaberg in the south — a total of 1,250 miles.
With roughly 3,000 coral reefs, 600 islands and 1,625 species of fish, the reef leaves its 1.6 million annual visitors enchanted."
</string>
    <string name="reef2">"But before diving in, it's important to get your bearings.
The northern half of the reef runs from the Cape York Peninsula to Cairns,
a popular home base for many reef visitors.
Not only does Cairns provide the closest reef access from the mainland,
 but it also boasts a few attractions of its own, like the Kuranda Scenic Railway and the Wildlife Habitat Port Douglas.
 Travel farther down the coast and you'll run into the southern half of the reef,
 which stretches from the Capricorn Coast (along the Tropic of Capricorn) to Gladstone and Fraser Island.
 Airlie Beach is a favored hub for travelers in the south thanks to its
 array of stylish resorts and its close proximity to a cluster of 74 islands known as the Whitsundays."</string>

    <string name="paris1">"The City of Light draws millions of visitors every year with its unforgettable ambiance.
 Of course, the divine cuisine and vast art collections deserve some of the credit as well.
 The gentle River Seine rambles through the city, flanked by stately museums,
 centuries-old churches, and blocks of Rococo- and Neoclassic-design architecture,
 further enhanced by charming trees and glowing streetlamps.
 Peppering the Seine's cobbled walks and graceful bridges are impossibly chic Parisians,
 probably on their way to the market, cafe or cinema."</string>

    <string name="paris2">" Containing world-class museums, fashion, cuisine, and an atmosphere all its own,
 Paris is also a city of "many splendors," as Ernest Hemingway recalled in his memoir, "A Moveable Feast."
 Visit the Centre Pompidou, enjoy gourmet pastries,
 shop couture on the Champs Élysées or hit the boutiques in Les Halles, take in the view atop the Eiffel Tower,
 or even plan a day trip to Versailles Palace.
 But don't miss out on the simple pleasure of meandering the marvelous arrondissements (districts)."
 </string>

    <string name="bora">
"The small island of Bora Bora (just 6 miles long and more than 2 miles wide) overflows with beauty.
Dormant volcanoes rise up at its center and fan out into lush jungle before spilling into an aquamarine lagoon.
In fact, author James Michener, who wrote "Tales of the South Pacific," called Bora Bora "the most beautiful island in the world."
The 18th-century British explorer James Cook even coined it as the "pearl of the Pacific."
The very definition of a tropical getaway,
blissful Bora Bora abounds with luxurious resorts, sunny skies, warm waters and friendly locals."</string>

    <string name="florence">"This little city, tucked amid the Tuscan hills, casts a long shadow through history.
The wellspring of the Renaissance, 
Firenze (or Florence) sheltered the powerful Medici family and inspired artists
 like Michelangelo (David) and Brunelleschi (the Duomo). 
 If it weren't for the fashionable Italians and 
 chic shops lining Via Tornabuoni, you might think you had traveled back in time to the 14th century. 
 But Renaissance art is not the only reason to come: You also visit Florence for its gorgeous sunsets, 
its Italian cooking and its unbeatable romantic charm."</string>
    
    <string name="tokyo1">""Animated" is perhaps the best word to describe Tokyo.
Crazy about its anime,Japan's mega city is constantly buzzing with movement—feet clack down sidewalks,
cars zoom along streets, subway trains hum below ground, ships cruise in and out.
And yet bright lights and loud signs beg you to pause,
to break your motion for just one second to pray (oops, we mean pay) at the altar of consumerism.
This is a city that feeds on motion and progress."</string>
    <string name="tokyo2">"But when you want to stop in Tokyo, the city will certainly make it worth your while.
The tech savvy locales may whizz past the monuments and 
urban parks daily (except during the cherry blossom season when everyone floods the green space), 
but, we assure you, the museums and historical sites are world-class. 
Here, there are photos to be taken, sushi to be eaten, and a lot of shopping to be done. 
So what are you waiting for? 
You better get a move on."</string>
    
    <string name="Rome">"Rome, the city of seven hills, enjoyed a mythic beginning.
Romulus and Remus — twin brothers who were nursed by a she-wolf and 
fathered by a war god — reportedly founded the Eternal City. 
And although historians are a little skeptical about this epic entry into the world, 
most travelers are absolutely certain that there is something magical about Rome. 
Whether it's the mystery of nearby Vatican City or the ghosts of the Colosseum, 
an afternoon caffè on Piazza Navona or a piled-high plate of pasta at a trattoria, Roma is sure to enchant."</string>
    
    <string name="cape">
"Sporty, stylish, stunning, sociable… If Cape Town was a person,
it would be that Hollywood starlet we all secretly envy. 
The Mother City is unlike any other destination in Africa: Separated from the rest of the continent by a ring of mountains, 
Cape Town stands as a glittering, metropolis juxtaposed with one of the world's most breathtaking natural landscapes. 
But good looks aren't the only thing Cape Town has going for it. You'll fall in love with this city's khaki-colored beaches, 
rolling vineyards, sizzling cuisine, thriving nightlife, and, of course, the spectacular Table Mountain. 
It may have taken an international soccer tournament to catch the world's attention, 
but since Cape Town took the global stage,no amount of buzzing vuvuzelas can drown out its magnificence. "</string>
    
    <string name="bercelona">"Barcelona contains both the authentically historic and the wildly bizarre.
From the tree-lined Las Ramblas to the narrow alleys of Barri Gòtic; 
from the beachside nightclubs to the city's dozens of sacred churches and cathedrals, 
this city by the sea seems to attract all types: 
the family, the adventurer, the couple, the backpacker, 
the culture lover — and more — with an almost overwhelming variety of things to do. 
You could stay for a few days, but chances are you'll need a whole week to explore."</string>
    
    <string name="amst">"Why Go to Amsterdam
Don't believe everything you hear about Amsterdam. 
Yes, this Netherlands city takes a lax look at women beckoning business in the Red Light District 
and "coffee shops" selling an unorthodox type of herb to a toking clientele, 
but these descriptions only scratch the surface. 
At some point, during an excellent Indonesian meal, 
a twilight canal-side rambling or a shopping excursion through the boutiques of Nine Little Streets, 
you'll realize – as many travelers have before you – that 
there's much more to Amsterdam than you might've thought."</string>
    
    <string name="cairo">"The desert heat, the noisy streets and the sheer size of Cairo will leave even the most adaptable traveler
with a serious case of culture shock.
The constant bombardment of street vendors,
the inescapable aroma of livestock and the seemingly chaotic way of life will joggle the senses.
But be patient. Take some time to relax over a cup of tea,
to wander the ancient streets and to watch the sun lower over the mighty Nile River.
It won't take long for the city's treasures to reveal themselves."</string>

    <string name="urlreef">http://travel.usnews.com/Great_Barrier_Reef_Australia/</string>
    <string name="urlparis">http://travel.usnews.com/Paris_France/</string>
    <string name="urlbora">http://travel.usnews.com/Bora_Bora/</string>
    <string name="urlflorance">http://travel.usnews.com/Florence_Italy/</string>
    <string name="urltokyo">http://travel.usnews.com/Tokyo_Japan/</string>
    <string name="urlitaly">http://travel.usnews.com/Rome_Italy/</string>
    <string name="urlcape">http://travel.usnews.com/Cape_Town_South_Africa/</string>
    <string name="urlberca">http://travel.usnews.com/Barcelona_Spain/</string>
    <string name="urlams">http://travel.usnews.com/Amsterdam_Netherlands/</string>
    <string name="urlcairo">http://travel.usnews.com/Cairo_Egypt/</string>

</resources>
